<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="cv.xsl"?>

<!DOCTYPE cv [
	<!ELEMENT cv (item)>
	<!ELEMENT item (title, inst, descrip, skills)>
	<!ATTLIST item qtrStart CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ATTLIST item qtrEnd CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ATTLIST item loc CDATA #REQUIRED>
	<!ELEMENT title (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT inst (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT descrip (#PCDATA)>
	<!ELEMENT skills (#PCDATA)>
	<!ATTLIST inst url CDATA #IMPLIED>
]>

<cv xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink">
	<item qtrStart="172" qtrEnd="present" loc="Seattle, Washington">
		<title>
			Graduate Student Researcher
		</title>
		<inst url="https://www.ess.washington.edu/people/profile.php?pid=harnett--erika">
			Harnett Group at U Washington
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Characterization of oceans on Europa, a moon of Jupiter. Comparison of spacecraft data to simulations of electromagnetic induction and the surrounding plasma environment.
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Fortran programming, <a href="https://pds.nasa.gov/index.shtml">NASA Planetary Data System (PDS),</a> Matlab, space plasma physics, plasma fluid modeling
		</skills>
	</item>
	
	<item qtrStart="162" qtrEnd="present" loc="Seattle, Washington">
		<title>
			Member, Board of Directors
		</title>
		<inst url="http://engage-science.com/">
			Engage program at U Washington
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			The Engage Board of Directors manages and runs the Engage science communication course.<br/>
			Roles: Webmaster, curriculum committee, application and screening committee, workshop facilitator
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Program administration, science communication training, PHP web management
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="124" qtrEnd="present" loc="Seattle, Washington">
		<title>
			Graduate Teaching Assistant
		</title>
		<inst url="https://www.washington.edu/">
			University of Washington
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Lead small-classroom discussion, tutorial, and laboratory meetings with undergraduate students.<br/>
			Three years as head TA for large (700-student) introductory physics classes.
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Formative assessment, Socratic dialogue, student engagement, classroom management<br/>
			As head TA: Course administration; iterative development for courses, curricula, test questions, and grading rubrics
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="141" qtrEnd="172" loc="Seattle, Washington">
		<title>
			Graduate Student Researcher
		</title>
		<inst url="http://depts.washington.edu/uwpeg/">
			Physics Education Group at the University of Washington (UWPEG)
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Study of student difficulties with flux and Gauss&apos;s law, curriculum development to address these difficulties.<br/>
			Study of student difficulties with interpreting diagrams representing three dimensions, development of interactive computing resources to address these difficulties.<br/>
			Webmaster
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Human subjects research and ethics, physics education research, curriculum development, exam design for research, vPython, HTML, Javascript, jQuery<br/>
			Drupal, PHP web management
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="132" qtrEnd="141" loc="Seattle, Washington">
		<title>
			Graduate Research Assistant
		</title>
		<inst url="http://faculty.washington.edu/seidler/">
			Seidler Group, U Washington and Argonne National Lab
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Study of <a href="http://cars9.uchicago.edu/xafs_school/APS_2005/Bare_XANES.pdf">X-ray absorption near-edge structure (XANES).</a> Data collection at <a href="https://www1.aps.anl.gov/">the Advanced Photon Source at ANL;</a> analysis of XANES data from molybdenum under high pressures (30 GPa), working toward characterization of shocked samples and <a href="http://www.lanl.gov/projects/dense-plasma-theory/background/warm-dense-matter.php">warm dense matter.</a>
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Python programming, hard X-ray spectroscopy R&amp;D, XANES, warm dense matter research
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="111" qtrEnd="123" loc="Davis, California">
		<title>
			Development Technician
		</title>
		<inst url="http://sanfordlab.org/experiment/lux-experiment">
			Large Underground Xenon (LUX) experiment
			UC Davis Interconnect Research Group
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Designed, built, studied, and analyzed a 1:2 scale analog of the LUX dark matter detector, for a proof-of-concept using piezoelectric microphones to triangulate bubble positions in cryogenic fluids.<br/>
			Restored and upgraded a damaged indium evaporation chamber used for <a href="http://www.palomartechnologies.com/blog/bid/28476/Solder-Bump-Bonding-Ball-Bumps-and-Wire-Bonds">bump bonding.</a>
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Cryogenic insulation and dewar design (still fluid, no boiling), cryogenic electronics, vacuum system fabrication, hardware interface design and fabrication, LabVIEW data recording and analysis
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="111" qtrEnd="114" loc="Davis, California">
		<title>
			Junior Specialist
		</title>
		<inst url="https://www6.slac.stanford.edu/">
			Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (SLAC) Linear Collider Research and Development (LCRD)
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Characterization of radiation damage of permanent magnets, analogous to use in linear collider beamlines. <a href="http://www.hep.uiuc.edu/LCRD/LCRD_UCLC_proposal_FY06/2_09_Pellett_BigDocFile.pdf">Click here for project summary.</a>
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			ROOT and C++ data analysis and visualization, LabVIEW data recording, radioactive sample handling, radiation environment protocol
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="104" qtrEnd="111" loc="Chooz, France">
		<title>
			Development Technician
		</title>
		<inst url="http://doublechooz.in2p3.fr/">
			Double Chooz neutrino experiment
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Shift leader, Double Chooz &quot;far&quot; detector filling operations. Simultaneous filling of thin-walled, concentric containers for liquid scintillators.
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			International collaboration and teamwork, clean room protocol, LabVIEW experiment monitoring
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="082" qtrEnd="104" loc="Davis and Berkeley, California">
		<title>
			Undergraduate Research Assistant
		</title>
		<inst url="http://fadley.physics.ucdavis.edu/">
			Fadley group, UC Davis and Lawrence Berkeley National Lab
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Restored an angle-resolved X-ray photoemission spectroscopy (ARXPS) system in disrepair to working order.<br/>
			Analyzed silicon wafers with ARXPS to determine surface oxide layer thickness<br/>
			<strong>Note:</strong> For more information, see my <a href="http://students.washington.edu/mjstyczi/documents/Styczinski_UG_thesis.pdf">undergraduate honors thesis.</a>
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Ultra-high vacuum systems (10<sup>-9</sup> Torr), X-ray photoemission spectroscopy (XPS), cryogen handling, angle-resolved photoemission materials characterization
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="083" qtrEnd="103" loc="Davis, California">
		<title>
			Course Reader (Physics 7)
		</title>
		<inst url="http://physics.ucdavis.edu/">
			UC Davis Physics Department
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Quiz handling, including scanning, data entry, and score calculation from grading codes; printing copies of in-class worksheets for thousands of students
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Scripting in FileMaker database software; large (1500-student) course administration
		</skills>
	</item>	
		
	<item qtrStart="074" qtrEnd="083" loc="Davis, California">
		<title>
			Lab Assistant
		</title>
		<inst url="http://airquality.crocker.ucdavis.edu/">
			IMPROVE Air Quality Group (Crocker Nuclear Lab)
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			First 5 months: Sample preparation and processing and data handling for IMPROVE air quality monitoring sites
			Next 6 months: Designed and carried out an experiment studying the impact of denuder pre-filtration on air quality sampling data.
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Use of delicate equipment e.g. mass balances; experiment design, data analysis and interpretation
		</skills>
	</item>

	<item qtrStart="063" qtrEnd="063" loc="Portola, California">
		<title>
			Assistant Mechanic
		</title>
		<inst url="http://www.whitecapreadymix.com/">
			White Cap Ready-Mix
		</inst>
		<descrip>
			Maintenance and repair tasks for cement mixers 
		</descrip>
		<skills>
			Basic technical skills, basic automotive maintenance and repair
		</skills>
	</item>	
</cv>
